Right now, begin to remove any barrier between your heart and the Spirit of God
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
The barrier could be offence, pain of the past or unforgiving spirit.
In Jesus Christ's name we pray.
Thank You, Lord!
See yourself free!
In the name of Jesus.
Say, "I'm free".
Say this with all your heart, "I'm free".
I can't hear you.
I'm free.
Yes, I'm free.
Right now, I command the power of God to come down, to come down upon you.
Power of God, come down, in the name of Jesus!
Every infirmity, wherever it is located, right now,
I command that infirmity in your blood, tendons, bones, - begin to command them out.
Command that infirmity.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Infirmity is associated with demon.
Right now, that spirit that causes infirmity, that demon, familiar spirit, begin to rebuke them.
Rebuke it.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus.
You demon - begin to rebuke that demon out of your life, out of your system.
Rebuke that demon!
I say to you, you demon, you infirmity...
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
I say to those infirmities, within and outside - out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You spirit, spirit of infirmity, I curse you, in the name of Jesus!
I say out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
I say out !
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Out!
Out, in the name of Jesus!
With all your sickness, failure, disappointment, setback, barrenness - command them out!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Demon, the spirit of infirmity is associated with sickness, disease, failure, disappointment -
all the challenges you are going through.
Right now, command them out with all their trouble.
You demon, out with all your troubles, failure!
I command you out of my life!
With all your trouble, disease, setback, limitation, failure, I command you out!
Say out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
You demon, with all your associations in my life, out!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Let me pray with you. I just need your 'Amen' with all your heart.
I want you to say 'Amen' with all your heart.
Let me pray with you; much can be achieved without noise.
Jesus knows you best.
Anywhere sickness, disease is located in your life, blood, tendons, kidneys, liver, fluids, bones,
on your skin, I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
Let the power of God come upon you!
Let the power of God come on you!
Say, "Power!"
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I speak to your finances.
I speak to your business.
I speak to your career. Let the story change!
Right now, let the story change!
You are free! Let the story change!
Let your story change - the story of your business, finances, career, marriage!
Story!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
When the story of your life changes, you will become an ex-loser.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I speak to your career, in the name of Jesus.
Let the power of God come on you.
Let the power of God come on your career, business, finances, marriage, money, family.
Power!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus!
I want you to be sincere.
Begin to mention your situation with all your heart,
and I will send the power of God upon it.
Right now, open your lips and begin to mention your situation, your challenges.
Open your lips, viewers all over the world.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers all over the world, I speak to your career, in the name of Jesus.
Let the power of God come on your career.
I speak to your finances, in the name of Jesus -
let the power of God come on your career.
I speak to your business, to your finances, to your career -
let the power of God come on them.
Power!
Viewers, when the power of God comes on your career, your career begins to flourish.
I want you to be under the influence of this telecast, under the influence of my voice.
I say, "Power!"
Let the power of God come on your business - power!
Let the power of God come on your career - power!
Let the power of God come on your life - power, in the name of Jesus!
Right now, history begin to change!
History about your business begin to change!
History about your life begin to change!
History about your finances begin to change!
History about you marriage and family begin to change!
Change!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers all over the world, I will not leave you.
I will speak to you many times; you deserve it.
I say to you:
Someone is busy changing your history.
Failure to ex-failure.
Sickness to good health.
Someone is busy changing your history.
In the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch The Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Thank You, Lord. Give thanks to God, give thanks to Him.
Give thanks to God.
Give thanks to Him.
Believe your history is changing.
Someone is busy changing your history.
Listen to me: Someone is busy changing your history.
Who is that Someone?
Jesus!
Tell your neighbour, "Someone is busy changing my history".
Changing my history, to I am healed, I am delivered, I am saved, I am free, in the name of Jesus.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Vomiting Blood and Poisonous Substances
Hallelujah!
Say to yourself, your heart, "Someone is busy changing my history".
History of your health - from sickness to good health.
History of your business - from failure to success.
History of your career - to great, great, great.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
In Jesus Christ's name.
Wave your hand and give thanks to God.
The Lord is good all the time.
If you know Someone is busy changing your file and your history, let me see your hand.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You would know next.
Next, you will know because you are not going to be the same.
I say, you are not going to be the same.
Can you confess this to your life?
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
You are not going to be the same.
Here you are, you are not going to be the same
Say, I'm not going to be the same.
My business, finances, career, future, marriage,
family are not going to be the same - Someone is busy changing my history!
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Why will you not remain the same?
Your business, finances, career, marriage, future are not going to be the same
because Someone is busy changing your history.
The SCOAN Sunday Mass Prayer
Wave your hand and say, Thank You, Lord".
Confess whom you are - "I am great in Christ Jesus!
In Christ Jesus, old things pass away. All things become new.
I'm born again. I'm saved. Jesus is my Saviour.
I'm healed. Jesus is my Healer.
I'm delivered. Jesus is my Deliverer.
I'm redeemed. Jesus is my Redeemer.
Begin to confess your position right now.
Confess your position, in the name of Jesus Christ.
Worship Him.
TT: Monica Asefa 15/12/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 25/12/2018
TT Monica Asefa